Guide to the Annette Weiner Papers MC 152
New York University Archives
- Series V: Conferences
  - Paris Conference, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Planning Conference, Irvine, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Preserving the Anthropological Record: Issues and Strategies, 1992 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Projection of the South: A Symposium on Folklore & Ethnography on Film and Videotape, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Royal Anthropological Institute: Film Conference, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - School of American Research Conference, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Sensuality, Power and Exchange Conference, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 8A)
  - SHERZER: 7th International Conference on Translation, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - The Temporal Texture of Textiles in Postmodernity, 1996-1997 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Wenner-Gren Conference: The Politics of Reproduction, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7904 0
  - Wenner-Gren Conference: Preserving the Anthropological Record: Issues and Strategies, 1992 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Wenner-Gren Conference: Anthropological Priorities in the Next Decade I, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Wenner-Gren Conference: Anthropological Priorities in the Next Decade II, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Series VI: Publication, papers, review and correspondences
  This series contains her publications from 1970s-1990s, reviews and correspondences on publications
  - Subseries I:
    This subseries contains Annette Weiners publications and papers from 1970s-1990s
    - Ethnohistory and Archeology in Colonial Antigua, Guatemala, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7905 7
    - A Preliminary Ceramic Analysis of Site Rc24, Santo Domingo Monastery, Antigua, Guatemala, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - The Cyclical Nature of Exchange, Ritual and Relationship in Kiriwina, Trobriand Islands (Draft), 1973 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Women of Value: the Main Road of Exchange in Kiriwina, Trobriand Islands, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Women of Value, Men of Renown: New Prospectives in Trobriand Exchange, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7906 5
    - La Richesse des Femmes :..., 1976 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Trobriand Descent: Female/ Male Domains, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Audiovisual Reviews from AAA: Epistemology and Ethnographic Reality..., 1978 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Toward a Tradition of Ethnographic Film Theory: ...(Early draft), 1978 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - The Reproductive Model in Trobriand Society, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Some Anthropological Observations: On Ritual in US-USSR Scientific Collaboration, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - The Sex Division of Labor, Development, and Women's Status, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Reproduction: a Replacement of Reciprocity, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - L'echange en Question: M. Mauss Victime de l'economisme, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Plus Precieux Que L'or: Relations et Echanges entre Hommes et Femmes Dans les Societes D'oceanie, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Reciprocite ou Reproduction aux Trobriand?, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Sexuality among the Anthropologists, Reproduction among the Informants, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Ten Years in the Life of an Island: the Anthropology of Development Policies in Trobriands (Draft), 1982 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - A World of Made is not a World of Born': Doing Kula in Kiriwina, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7907 3
    - Ethnographic Determinism: Samoa and the Margaret Mead Controversy, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Why Cloth? Reflections on the Meaning of Cloth as Object of Exchange (Papers, not for publication), 1983 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Du Sexe des Anthropologues, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Inalienable Wealth, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Oedipus and Ancestors, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Cloth and the Organization of Human Experience, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Piu' Prezioso dell'oro: ...., 1986 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - The Bronislaw Malinowski Sexual Life of Savages: Introduction, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Cloth and Human Experience, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7908 1
    - La Kula et la Quete de la Renommee, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Why Cloth? Wealth, Gender, and Power in Oceania, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Stoffe: Reichtum, Geschlecht und Macht in Ozeanien, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Book Reviews: Trobriand Islanders, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Trobrianders on Camera and Off the Film that did not Get Made, 1990-1994 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7909 9
    - Keeping-While-Giving: Sibling Incest and Gender, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Reproduction and Social Theory, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Anthropology's Lesson for Cultural Diversity..., 1992 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Reviews on Kitawa: a Linguistic and Aethetic Analysis of Visual Art in Melanesia, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Community: Antidote for the Isolated Family, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Cultural Difference and the Density of Objects, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Cloth that does not Die: Foreword, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Culture and our Discontents, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - From Words to Objects to Magic: Hard Words and the Boundaries of Social Interaction, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7910 7
    - Japanese and German Publications, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Malinowski's Diary (Article), undated (Box 101, Folder 2A)
    - Reciprocity-Cultural Difference and Density of Objects, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - The Gift Reconsidered (Fowler Museum Papers), undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - The Sibling Incest Taboo: Polynesia Cloth and Reproduction, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - The Trobriand Islanders of Papua New Guinea, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Trobriand Kinship from Another View: the Reproductive Power of Women and Men, undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Subseries II:
    This subseries contains her reviews on other publications, reviews on her publications by various authors and correspondences on publications
    - American Ethnological Society: Correspondence and Keynote Lecture on "Cultural Difference and the Density of Objects", 1993 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7911 5
    - Anthropology Newsletter: review by Annette Weiner on "California Dreaming", 1992 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Beacon Press: Contract on "Women and Colonization: Anthropological Perspectives", 1978 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Beacon Press: Introduction on " Sexual Life of Savages in Northwestern Melanesia", 1986-1987 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Beacon Press: Contracts on Kula papers, undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Behavior Today Newsletter: Correspondence on presentation of papers on Trobriand Islands, Paris, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Bibliography for Anthropology Publications, undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - California State University, Sacramento: review progress of the Death Project, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Cazeneuve, Jean: review on "La Richesse des Femmes", 1983 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Choice: Review on "Inalienable Possessions:...", 1993 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - The Chronicle of Higher Education: Cultural Analysis at NYU, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Concordia University: Correspondence on publishing of "Inalienable Possessions"-- etc., 1991 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence on AW's Biographical Data during 1979-1980 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - AW's Biography from Book, undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Correspondences on 'Inalienable Possessions", 1992 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Correspondences on Publication in 'The Chronicle'/ Responses, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Correspondences on Trobriands' Publications, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Ecole des Hautes Etudes: Correspondences on Publications, 1993-1994 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Editions Du Seuil, 1976-1982 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Encyclopedia Americana: The Scope of Archeology, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Encyclopedia Americana: Correspondences on "The Scope of Archeology", 1994 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Grenada Television Limited: Correspondence on her Article " The Trobriand Islanders", 1986-1994 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Grenada Television Limited: Film Talk & Workshop, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Hassig, Ross: Correspondence on Review of Ethnohistory, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7912 3
    - Holt, Rinehart and Winston; Correspondences on Trobriands, 1984-1993 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Howlett, Marc V.: 'Affaires de Femmes' (review on Annette Weiner's article), 1983 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Human Behavior, News magazine: Annette Weiner's Publication on 'Women of Value, Men of Renown", 1978-1979 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Human Relations Area Files, Inc: Correspondence and Bibliography about Trobriand Islands, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Lantz, Pierre: Translate Annette Weiner's article on "A change in Paradigm in Anthropology?", undated (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Leach, Edmund: review on "Virgin Birth", 1966-1968 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Leach, Edmund: review on "Trobriand Medusa", undated (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Leach, Edmund: review on "Women of Value, Men of Renown:..., undated (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Lepowski, Maria: review on " Inalienable Possession:..." and Annette Weiner's response, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - L'Homme: review on " Inalienable Possession:...", 1994 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - MAN, Journal of the Ritual Anthropologist Institute: Correspondence on Publishing article, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous requests on publications, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Morell, Virginia: 'Science' article about Annette Weiner, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Nash, Jill: reviews be Annette Weiner on "Matriliny and Modernisation", 1980 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities: Correspondences about publication information, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Correspondences on Trobriands' article, 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - New York Times: book reviews and responses on "Inalienable Possessions", 1992 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Northwestern University: Anthropology Department Review, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - NYU Today: News about Annette Weiner become a new Dean of GSAS, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Oceania: reviews on "Dominant Kings and Forgotten Queens", 1988 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Pacific Studies: Annette Weiner's Rejoinder to reviews of "Inalienable Possessions", 1995 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Publications: Responses/ Inquiries/ Feedback, 1993-1994 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Reprints articles on 'Wedding Gifts", 1992 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Routledge: review and report on publication of projects' entitled "Companion Encyclopedia of Anthropology...", 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Routledge: review on "Naturalizing Power" edited by Sylvia Yanagisako and Carol Delaney, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Sano, Toshiyuki: Correspondences on Translation of Cloth and Human Experience, 1992-1993 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 0405 7913 1
    - School of American Research: Correspondence about Seminar proposal on "Transpositions of Material Culture", 1993 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Smithsonian Institution Press: Annette Weiner's reviews on "Cloth"- Cloth Volume- Letters on Cloth- Correspondences- Miscellaneous, 1983-1987 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - The College of William & Mary: News and correspondences on 'Gandhi Achievement Award' & 'Gandhi Lecture", 1992 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - University of California, L.A.: correspondences on the progress of "The Art of Giving", 1992-1993 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - University of California Press: review "Cloth", 1984 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - University of California Press: Inalienable Possessions, 1990-1991 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - University of California Press: review by Annette Weiner on "Nuer Dilemmas", 1995 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - University of Texas Press: Women of Value...Reviews, undated (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - University of Texas Press: Correspondences on "Women of Value...", 1974-1985 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Weiner, Annette B.: "Forward" for Renne's book, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Weiner Annette's reprints on Editorships and Correspondence on Editorships, 1993-1995 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Weiner, Annette B.: "Trobrianders on Camera and Off" and Correspondences, 1992-1993 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Weiner, Annette B.: Yearly Review of Anthropology (Draft), undated (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Wolf, Margery: review by Annette Weiner on "Reducing the Puzzlement: Postmodernism, Feminism, and Ethnographic Responsibility", undated (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Women of Value, Men of Reknown...., undated (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Young, Michael W.: book review by Annette Weiner on "The Trobriand Islands 1915-1918", 1979 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Young, Michael W.: book review by Annette Weiner on "Magicians of Manumanua, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- Series VII: Studies
  This series contains her studies at Bryn Mawr College: Lecture Notes from 1967-1973, Papers from 1966-1971, Articles from 1967-1972, and other studies
  - Physical Anthropology 524 course: lecture notes, reading lists, and final examination, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7914 9
  - Notes on Culture Change in Archeology, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Kroeber, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Notes on 'Technology Seminar", 1969 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Notes on 'North American Indians Seminar", 1969 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Notes on 'South America Seminar", 1969 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Reviews reading on 'Personality and Culture Seminar,' Lecture notes, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - American Archaic Seminar: lecture notes, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Anthropology 645 course: notes, syllabus and archeology field methods, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Arctic Archeology Problem: Ceramics notes and articles, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Notes on Teire' Social Organization, from seminar in 1970 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7915 6
  - Notes on Behavioral Evolution, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Notes on reprints series in S. Organization Seminar- Goodale, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Boreal People notes, from 'Seminar on Boreal Peoples", 1970-1971 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Notes on History and Theory, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Australia Seminar (BMC), 1973 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Notes on Cambridge Series, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 6A)
  - Notes on Oceania: Polynesia, undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Culture Area: North and South America, undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Bear Ceremonalism report and notes, undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Articles and notes on 'Community Culture Seminar: Caribbean Area', 'Jamaican Elite", undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Reprint article and notes on 'Nativistic Monuments", undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Anthropology 502 course: Paper on 'Old World Neolithic", 1966-1967 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7916 4
  - Paper on 'Methodology in Sub-Human Primate Behavior Studies", 1967 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology 500 course: Paper on 'An Examination of the Art Tradition of an Early Neolithic Site in the Near East", 1967 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Anthropology 500 course: Paper on 'Dendrochronology and Radiocarbon Dating Methods", 1967 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Anthropology 652 course: Paper on 'Emile Durkheim", 1968 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Senior Thesis on 'A History of Anthropological Theory and Cultural Pluralism in the British West Indies", 1968 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Grant Proposal (North American Archeology): A Technical Survey of the Ceramic Ware from the Archaic and Formative Periods in Guatemala, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Paper on 'Child Socialization: Play, Playmates, and Elder Statesmen", 1969 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Paper on North American Indian Seminar: 'A Survey of Cult Movements Among Western Indian Tribes During the 19th Century, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Paper on Nativistic Movements Among North American Indians, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Paper on South American Indian Seminar and Open book examination, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Paper on 'Statistical Analysis of Questionnaire Data", 1969 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Paper on 'Redfield Goodale", 1969 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Paper on 'The Postclassic Periods in Highland Guatemala", 1970 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Paper on 'Theory, Research and Nonunilinear Descent", 1970 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Paper on 'Politiking and Trading Among North Alaskan Eskimos", 1971 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Urban Anthropology course: Paper on Peasant Seminar: 'Rich man, Poor Man' in the Rural-Urban Continuum, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Paper on 'Kroeber and Tylor' by Mc Neary, Stephen, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Brown Paper, on Malinowski's Exchange Theory, undated (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Bastrop Working Project: Correspondences & Notes, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Bastrop Working Project: Proposal for research in Bastrop Texas, by Adler, Marianna, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Anthropology 500 course: lecture and final examination, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7917 2
  - Outline of Seminar on South American Indians, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - North American Indian Seminar: bibliography, reading comment, and notes, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Seminar on African Prehistoric Behavior Patterns: Topic for discussion, suggested readings, and lectures, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Bibliography on Boreal Peoples, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Bibliography on Polynesia: Tikopia, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Article on 'An Introduction to the Peoples and Cultures of Micronesia", 1972 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Article on 'Prehistory of west Mexico", undated (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Series VIII: Professional Organizations
  This series contains the stuff in her professional organizations joining, especially AAA
  - AAA's Correspondence 1989-1990 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7918 0
  - AAA's Correspondence 1992 (January-July) (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - AAA's Correspondence 1992 (August-December) (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - AAA's Correspondence 1993 (January-May) (Box 110, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7919 8
  - AAA's Correspondence 1993 (June-December) (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - AAA's Correspondence 1994 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - AAA's Correspondence 1995-1996 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- About AAA Headquarters Move, 1991-1992 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 7920 6
  - AAA's Board of Directors & AAA's Presidents of Units, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Active Funding Raising, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Letter to Yvonne Kenedy: Building Purchase Offer, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Committee on Minority Relations-Meeting of the Academic Relations Committee, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Development Plan, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Dinner on September 8th, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- 'Editor-in Chief ", 1992 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Executive Director Search Committee, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Government Ethics, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Long Range Planning, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Long Range Planning Committee, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Memberships, Staff, Fellows, Subcommittees, and AAA's Mailing List, undated (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Planning Goal (5-10 years), 1989 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Presidential Awards Nominees, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- President-Elect (Annette Weiner won the election), 1989 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- President-Elect, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- President's Report, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Presidential Lecture, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Publication's Meetings, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- 'Renewable Natural Resources Issues for the 21st Century", 1991 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- The National Science Foundation (NSF) Directorate, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Unit Organization, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - AAA's Board of Directors- Unit Organization, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - AAA's Board of Directors-Unit Requests, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - AAA's Budget- Statement of Portfolio Valuation, 1991-1993 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8041 0
  - AAA's Budget- Potential Uses of AAA Endownment Funds, undated (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - AAA's Budget- Finance Committee's Letter, 1992-1993 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - AAA's Budget- Finance Committee, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - AAA's Budget- The Sullivan Principles, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - AAA's Budget- Financial Planning Report, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - AAA's Publications- Commission on Publications Policy, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - AAA's Publications- Correspondences on Publications, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Anthropology Newsletter on President-Elect, 1989, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 7A)
  - AAA's Publications- Anthropology and Humanism Quarterly, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - AAA's Publications- 'Archives' (Resolution on Preserving Anthropological Records), 1992 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - AAA's Publications- Journal distribution, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - AAA's Publications- October, 1992 Publications Meeting (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - AAA's Publications- Program Complaints, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - AAA's Publications- The Anthropology Newsletter, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - AAA's Annual Meeting- Film Symposium, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8042 8
  - AAA's Meeting- Proposal for Organized Session, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - AAA's Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - AAA's Annual Meeting- Presidents' Meeting, 1990 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - AAA Meeting and meeting schedule, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - AAA's Annual Meeting- Russian Anthropology Sessions, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - AAA's Annual Meeting- Mexican Anthropology Sessions, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - AAA's Annual Meeting- Multiculturalism Sessions, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - AAA Meeting, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - AAA Meeting, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - AAA's External Affairs- Bones, Human Skeletal Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8043 6
  - AAA's External Affairs- Correspondences on CAIL (The Conference on American Indian Languages), 1991 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - AAA's External Affairs- Meeting on Funding Anthropology, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - AAA's External Affairs- National Science Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - AAA's External Affairs- Study the Academic Employment of Women in Anthropology, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - AAA's External Affairs- The Hopi Tribe, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - AAA's External Affairs- The Tasaday Controversy, 1991-1993 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - AAA's External Affairs- Yanomami Commission, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - AAA's External Affairs- Washington Contacts, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - AAA's External Affairs- An Agenda for the 1990s (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Bronitsky, Gordon, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 0405 8044 4
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Buikstra, Jane (Memo), 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- President's Report, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - AAA's Personal Correspondence- Collier, George A., 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 3)